Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series XIV. Miscellaneous
  - Tuberculin Record Book, 1922-1928 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Record of sales of TB tests made by the College
  - Visitors-Guest Books, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Visitors-Guest books, 1960-1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Women in the College (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Proclamations and Legislative Resolutions, 1980, 1982, 1994, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Governor's Citations, 1982, 1994, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Visitors - Guestbooks, 1967-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Visitors - Guestbook, 1957-1978 (Box 19)
  - News Clippings, 1896, 1904, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings - oversized, 1902 (Box 9)
  - News Clippings, 1930s (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings, 1940-1943 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - News Clippings, 1950-1959 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - News Clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - News Clippings, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - News Clippings, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - News Clippings - oversized, 1970s and 1980s (Box 9)
  - News Clippings, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings, 1990s (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Visitors-Guest Book, 1957-1978 (Box 19)
  - Unidentified handwritten abstracts, 1890s (Box 22)
  - College Centennial Calendar, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - College Note Cards and Stationery with College Images, 1990s (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Joseph Dye's medals, 1929, 1952; MU-1540 (Box 37)
  - Dean William Hagen's paperweight, no date; MU-1543 (Box 37)
  - Cooper print plate, photo negative of faculty, no date; MU-1541 (Box 37)
  - Surgical Instruments made by Leach and Green of England and Scotland and presented to John P. Burke in 1961, no date; MU-1542 (Box 37)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Avian, no dates (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Bovine, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Dogs, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Equine - some slides, 1980s-2003 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Exotic Wildlife, 1970s-2001 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Exotic Wildlife - slides, 1980s-2000 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Felines, 1970s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Felines - slides, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - General Microbiology, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Horses - Slides, 1980s-2001 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Infectious Disease - slides, 1980s (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Mice - slides, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Objects - slides, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - People - slides and CDs, 1990s-2004 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - People - slides, 1980s-2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - People, 1980s-2001 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - People and Pets - some slides, 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Radiology - some slides, 1990s-2000 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Research - some slides, 2000s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Science Images - some slides, no dates (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Surgery - Slides, 1970s-2001 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Woodchucks, no dates (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Artwork in College, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Bookmark, no date (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - "A Century of Bovine Medicine at Cornell" - Draft - Eileen Roberts, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Logo, no date (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Daniel Salmon Charcoal Etching - Conservation Information, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Timeline - History, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 12)